Previously on Friends...
How did the job stuff go?
He offered me one.
You know what? This calls for a bottle
of Israels finest.
The job is in Paris.
Oh, God! Please, somebody say
something.
So if you take this job you'll be
moving to Paris?
Or facing a bitch of a commute.
I know, it's huge and it's scary,
and it's... really far, far away from
you guys
but this is such an incredible
opportunity for me.
And I've already talked to them about
our situation with Emma and they said
they'll do whatever we need to make us
feel comfortable.
- Okay. - I mean, I'll fly back and
forth
- they'll fly you out... Anything we
want. - My boss said I might be getting
a new lamp in my cubicle.
All right, we'll work it out. Thank
you! Thank you! Yeah, yeah!
You sure this is what you want?
I think it is.
Ooh, what's going on?
I got a really incredible job offer.
Hey, great! All right! Good for you!
It's in Paris.
What? No, no, no! No, no... no... no,
no...
No, too much is changing, okay?
First, Phoebe getting married
Congratulations!
Nd then these two move into a stupid
house in the stupid suburbs...
Hey, this afternoon you said you'd be
supportive...
Well, it comes and goes. I wouldn't
trust it.
Look, you guys... this is really,
really important to me.
And it means a lot if you could try to
get on board.
Of course we can. Congratulations.
Yay! - Joey... - No, no, no.
My hugs are reserved for people STAYING
IN AMERICA.
Joey, it would mean so... Hey! No! Get
your France-going-arms away from me.
Joey...
You okay with this?
Well, it makes me feel sad, but...
Talking to Ross. I see.
Well, Rachel moving to another country?
Not being able to see her every day.
How can I be okay with this?
I know, but what are we gonna do? She
really needs this job.
Do you think if the Ralph Lauren people
offered her her old job back, she would
take it?
How is that gonna happen? Is this the
best way to use one of your three magic
wishes?
I don't know. I could talk to her boss.
Yeah! I met him at that Christmas
party.
We really hit it off.
You mean the guy who kept calling you
Ron?
I didn't say we were brothers.
Friends - 10x15 - Estelle Dies
华南木棉@meitina
美天乐工作室-Meitina
Adjusted by Madhero
Hey Phoebe.
Hey, tell me what you think. All right.
The house next door to the one that
we're buying in Westchester? Just went
on the market.
I wanna take a look at it, but Chandler
doesn't.
We close escrow tomorrow, so seeing
another house can only confuse us
and we're easily confused. We're not
very bright.
But what if it is better than ours?
Should we at least look?
What do you think Pheebs?
Well, I think that shirt makes you look
like you should work at a Baskin
Robbins...
Anyway...
Hey, isn't Joey's agent Estelle
Leonard?
Yeah. She died.
You're kidding! That's terrible!
Yeah, last Saturday. Wow!
She was the first black man to fly solo
across the Atlantic.
Oh, wait a minute, I read the wrong
one.
Oh yeah? Yeah, she was just an agent.
Joey's gonna be so upset.
I know. He always wanted to be the
first black man to cross the Atlantic.
Well, we cannot tell Joey about this.
He's already flipping out about
everything that's changing.
This will push him over the edge.
Seriously, you don't think we should
tell him?
Well, not for a little while. Let's
just give him a few days to get used to
everything else.
What if he reads it in the paper?
Unless Snoopy says it to Charlie Brown,
I think we're okay.
May I help you?
Yeah, I'm a friend of Rachel Green's.
Uhm, actually we met at the Christmas
party about two years ago.
Oh right, uhm, Don? Close. Ron.
Uh... What can I do for you?
Uhm, well... I'm here to see if you'll
give Rachel her job back.
Ah, did she ask you to come here and do
this?
Oh, no. Then we'll see if she wants to
come back. At first I have to get you
to agree.
Wow, that is tempting.
Look, she loved her job here.
And let's face it you're not gonna find
anyone who did it as well as she did
it. Isn't that true?
She is good! Huh, I took a shot there.
But I'm sorry. There's nothing I can
do...
Ah, it's not true, there is... nothing
I want to do.
I see... Thanks very much.
Is this your son?
Yeah, his name is Ross.
What?
Oh, nothing, it's just, it's close to
Ron.
Does he... Does little Ross like
dinosaurs by any chance?
Yeah, they're all he talks about, why?
How would he like to come with me to
the Museum of Natural History
after everyone else has left just the
two of us,
and he can touch anything he wants.
I just heard it as you must have heard
it and that's not good. Let me start
again.
I'm a paleontologist
you'll be there with us and the
touching refers only to bones -
fossils!
You can really arrange that?
You let Rachel come back, and it's
done.
Well, I guess having Rachel back
wouldn't be the worst thing in the
world.
Yeah! Yes! Thank you! This is great.
Thank you so much.
And I swear, your kid is going to have
the time of his life.
That's great. I worry about little
Ross.
He's always reading, he's collecting
rocks and he's obsessed with dinosaurs.
He'll be fine.
Hey Phoebe.
Hey. Everything ok?
I'm just mad at my agent.
Estelle? Why?
There's a part in a TV movie that I
would be perfect for and I didn't even
be put up for it!
She'd better have a good reason.
I'm guessing she does.
Well I'm wanna hear it, because she
keeps doing this.
Well, no, no, wait, wait, wait. All
right, I gotta go.
Just listen. Promise me, that you will
wait a minute before you call her.
Ok. Why?
Because a promise between friends means
never having to give a reason.
I love that saying!
Hello? Joey, it's Estelle.
I was just gonna call you! That's
weird.
It's a little coincidental, but
believable.
Listen, I'm sure you're wondering
why I didn't get you an audition for
that TV movie.
Yeah, actually I am!
I guess I dropped the ball there.
Whoopsie!
That's it? You know, it seems all you
do lately is drop the ball.
Don't take that tone with me. Who you
think you are?
Alan Lemond, the first black man to fly
solo across the Atlantic?
No, no, look. All I'm saying is that
you're my agent, ok?
And you're not getting me into any
auditions and I'm tired of it.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that This isn't working for
me anymore, ok? Estelle, you're fired.
Goodbye.
Man, tough week for Estelle!
Hi. Hi.
Emma left her stuffed t-rex at my
house.
You know she can't sleep without it.
Oh, well, she's asleep now. Stop
forcing that thing on her.
Ok.
Oh, you're not gonna believe what
happened to me today!
Ralph Lauren called, and gave me my job
back!
Nooo!
Yee. I mean, it was so weirdest thing.
They fired me and then out of nowhere
they just hire me back!
I mean, that place must have been
falling apart without me.
So, you're not going to Paris.
No, I'm still going.
Wh - wh - what?
When the Louis Vuitton people found out
that Ralph Lauren wanted me back
- they offered me more money! Isn't
that great? - Yeeeah!
Hi. We're buying the house next door
and we were wondering if we could just
take a look around.
Oh, sure. I'm showing it to someone
else right now but please, look around.
Thanks.
It feels like we're cheating on our
house.
And if we're gonna cheat, shouldn't it
be with like a hot younger house, that
does stuff that our house won't do?
Ours is so much better!
This living room is smaller, the dining
room looks like a cave! What a hole!
So? What do you think?
Love it!
Well, we already have one offer on it
and I think the lady upstairs is goning
to make another one.
They could be our neighbors, what are
they like?
Oh, the woman upstairs is very nice.
She and her husband have two kids, he's
on Wall Street and she -
Oh my God!
Sure.
Hey Joey, want come with me to
- are you ok?
Yeah, I just - I just feel bad about
firing Estelle. This is got to be
killing her.
No, that wouldn't kill her. Ordinary
embolism might.
I don't know. She's got to be taking it
hard, I was like her only client.
Except for this guy who eats paper.
And I'm guessing he eats more money
than he makes.
Look, I know she's not a great agent,
but she did stick with me for ten
years.
I'm gonna call her and hire her again.
No, no, no! Don't call her! You wait
for her to call you
- Why? - Because patience is the road
to understanding
which... is the key... to a happy
heart.
You blow me away.
All right, so promise you're gonna wait
for her to call you?
I promise. And that means, never having
to give a reason.
What a small world!
And yet I never run into Beyonce!
You two know each other?
Oh, we go way back. Before Monica made
an honest man out of him
Chandler used to be my little love
muffin! Heh-heh-heh!
So? Are you guys thinking of getting
this house too?
Ooh! Are we gonna have a bidding war?
I'd better warn you, I'm a toughie
Don't, don't!
No, actually, we're buying the house
next door.
Why!?
I don't know why.
Ooh, that decides it then.
I was on the fence. But knowing that
you two would be our neighbors?
Ah! Now we have to get it! Ellen, we're
going to talk numbers.
This can not be happening!
Okay, the realtor said another couple
made an offer.
Maybe the Janice's won't get it! Maybe
the other couple will.
The only way that that is going to
happen, is if the other couple are the
Hitlers.
Okay, Okay All right. What if we got
both houses? Huh? We can turn this
house into a guest house.
That is a great idea! And by the way, I
don't mean to sound distasteful but
when did you start crapping money!?
Okay, you come up with an idea.
Alright alright we still have three
hours till escrow closes on our house
We can still get out.
But we love our house.
Will we love it so much with her next
door?
And she's gonna be louder out here too.
Just the crickets and "Oh My God"!
Okay, but if we don't get this house
she's still gonna show up wherever we
go!
I mean, at least if she's here, it
eliminates the element of surprise.
I mean, never again will you have to
hear the three words...
...that make your balls jump back up
inside your body.
Well, we have to do something. We can't
have her living next door.
Oh, that does it too.
Who is it?
It's me. Ron.
Look, I um, I now Rachel turned you
down
but I think there is a way you might be
able to get her to come back.
This may surprise you but re-hiring
fired employees, is not my main job.
Just hear me out. How would you feel
about offering her a raise?
Not good, Ron.
Perhaps I can persuade you.
What if you can give your son this
genuine pterodactyl egg replica.
Wow, that's pretty cool
Huh? So? We have a deal?
Okay, you got it. Yes! Yes!
This is gonna make me very popular.
Oh, Believe me, the ladies, they love
it!
I meant with my son.
Good, 'cause the ladies, not so much.
Joey, this is Al T. Booker, the guy who
eats paper.
I'm sure you've heard that Estelle
passed away.
I wanted to let you know there's a
memorial for her...
...at the Westside chapel, tomorrow at
ten. Hope you can make it.
Oh my God.
Hello?
Joey, it's Estelle.
Estelle?
Yeah, I wanted to call and tell you
that there's no hard feelings for
firing me.
Ok-ay. I just, I can't believe you're
calling me?
Well, I didn't think I should just drop
by...
No, no, no! Don't drop by, don't drop
by!
Anyway, you did what you had to do. I'm
okay.
Can I ask you something?
Uhm, what's it like there?
It's alright. Look kiddo, I gotta go.
Good luck with the career. You're gonna
be huge.
Thanks for everything Estelle. Bye.
"Out of area". Boy, I'll say.
Well... I just talked to Sid
we are definitely putting in an offer
on the house...
a-a-and I'll bet we get it. The Hitlers
will be so disappointed.
All right, I got to run. Tell Monica I
say goodbye.
And... I'll see you later, neighbor.
Wait! I just want you to know that...
I'm so happy you're going to be here.
Oh, me too...
Because... that way...
we can pick up where we left off.
Huh?
I never stopped loving you.
Oh... my...
Yeah, yeah, yeah! I want you... I need
you...
I must have you Janice Litman Goralnik
Neihosenstein.
Chandler, what are you talking about?
Now that you live next door, we can be
together every day. Sid and Monica
never have to know a thing.
I don't know what to say...
I mean, you know, obviously we have
this... heat between us.
Obviously.
But I love my husband. And I know you
love your wife.
Now, I don't think we should get this
house now.
Don't say that. Don't tangle the dream
and take it away.
Chandler, one of us has got to be
strong.
I understand.
Although, maybe just... one last moment
of weakness...
Goodbye Chandler Bing.
They're never coming down now.
Hi!
Hey! You are never going to believe
what happened to me today.
What?
Ralph Lauren called again and they
offered me more money.
They did? Yeah. It was the weirdest
thing.
Zelner called me and he said we'll do
everything we can to get you back.
And that I should thank some Ron... I
don't even know what department that
guy's in.
So, what are you gonna do?
Well, I took it. That's great! So
you're staying in New York!
YAY! WHOO! YAY! You're excited, right?
Ye-ah. Yeah! You know, the money's
great. It's certainly the easier
choice...
Right!
Yeah, you know, was I looking forward
to going to Paris?
Sure. You know, was I excited about
working in the fashion capital of the
world?
Ooh, absolutely... Oh...! Yeah, but you
know, this is... it's fine.
I'm fine going back to a job where I've
pretty much gotten everything out of
that I possibly can...
Uhm, I hadn't no you...
I had no idea you were so excited about
Paris.
Uhm, I mean, you said you were scared.
Well yeah, but I mean, it was good
scared though, you know?
Like when l-moved-to-New-York scared.
Or uhm, when
l-found-out-l-was-gonna-have-Emma
scared...
But this is... fine. This is gonna be
good.
You should go.
What?
It's what you want. You should go.
You really think so?
I really do.
But I already told Zelner that I would
come back...
I'm sure he'll understand.
All right. ALL RIGHT! I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna go to Paris.
Yeah...
Yeah! I'm going to Paris. Thank you,
Ross!
Yeah, yeah, oh! Oh! Oh, I'm so happy.
Then I'm happy too.
Thank you all for coming.
We're here today to pay respects to a
wonderful agent and a beautiful
woman...
...inside.
As Estelle's only two clients we would
like to say a few words.
Dude, where's my speech?
That is entertaining. Al Zebooker
everybody.